var questions=[
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "",
        answer : "Angola",
        options : [
            "Angola",
            "Iraq",
            "Ethiopia",
            "Sudan",
        ]
    },
    {
    num : 2,
    question : "",
    answer : "Niger",
    options : [
        "Libya",
        "Niger",
        "Moldova",
        "Estonia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 3,
    question : "",
    answer : "Ethiopia",
    options : [
        "Montenegro",
        "Andorra",
        "Ethiopia",
        "Finland",
    ]
},
{
    num : 4,
    question : "",
    answer : "Egypt",
    options : [
        "DR Congo",
        "Egypt",
        "Malta",
        "Mali",
    ]
},
{
    num : 5,
    question : "",
    answer : "Morocco",
    options : [
        "Vatican City",
        "Guernsey",
        "Morocco",
        "Nigeria",
    ]
},
{
    num : 6,
    question : "",
    answer : "Zambia",
    options : [
        "Zambia",
        "Latvia",
        "Albania",
        "North Macedonia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 7,
    question : "",
    answer : "Libya",
    options : [
        "Madagascar",
        "Zimbabwe",
        "Kenya",
        "Libya",
    ]
},
{
    num : 8,
    question : "",
    answer : "Senegal",
    options : [
        "Senegal",
        "Togo",
        "Liberia",
        "Burundi",
    ]
},
{
    num : 9,
    question : "",
    answer : "Zimbabwe",
    options : [
        "Djibouti",
        "Gambia",
        "Zimbabwe",
        "Mauritius",
    ]
},
{
    num : 10,
    question : "",
    answer : "Uganda",
    options : [
        "Kenya",
        "Burkina Faso",
        "Ghana",
        "Uganda",
    ]
},
{
    num : 11,
    question : "",
    answer : "Botswana",
    options : [
        "Botswana",
        "Spain",
        "Uganda",
        "Benin",
    ]
},
{
    num : 12,
    question : "",
    answer : "Kenya",
    options : [
        "Togo",
        "Lesotho",
        "Kenya",
        "Kazakhstan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 13,
    question : "",
    answer : "Liberia",
    options : [
        "Belarus",
        "Liberia",
        "Albania",
        "Seychelles",
    ]
},
{
    num : 14,
    question : "",
    answer : "Tunisia",
    options : [
        "São Tomé and Príncipe",
        "Seychelles",
        "Eswatini",
        "Tunisia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 15,
    question : "",
    answer : "Rwanda",
    options : [
        "Cape Verde",
        "Comoros",
        "Rwanda",
        "Senegal",
    ]
},
{
    num : 16,
    question : "",
    answer : "Burundi",
    options : [
        "Djibouti",
        "Burundi",
        "Kenya",
        "Tanzania",
    ]
}
];